lsbet.com 2017-07-05

# LSbet.com - Privacy Policy

When registering with LSbet.com you will be asked to provide us with sensitive client information such as: name, valid address with postcode, date of birth, email address, account and credit card details etc. We also collect your details every time you contact us or information about the transactions you initiate including details of the payment cards used.  
Your personal information will be used for purposes such as setting up and managing your account, customer profiling, security and marketing. All customer data will be treated confidential and will not be sold to others.

At LSbet.com we use "cookies".A cookie is a small piece of information sent by the web server to the web browser that gets entered into the memory of your browser and collects information from it. Cookies are used to identify customers' preferred language so that this is automatically selected at the next visit, to ensure the client receives any bonuses he is eligible for or to keep track of your browsing patters. If you do not want us to use cookies please turn cookies off from your browser.

The communication between you and LSbet.com is secured employing a 256-bit Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology encryption, therefore a maximum security is offered. All your personal information including your credit card details are encrypted so that these cannot be read while travelling through Internet.

If our site contains any links to outside parties, LSbet.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or content of any subsequent site that doesn't belong to LSbet.com. These sites may collect information from you and use it according to their own privacy policy which can differ from ours.

When you play casino slots developed by NetEnt, NetEnt’s privacy policy also applies. It can be found here.
